Hello There!

I have created a simple GAIndicator which helps you as a plug in.
The plug in files here are GAIndicator.h & GAIndicator.m and this is a sample project.

Some times we think of creating a Custom Activity Indicator for iOS apps. So I thought we can implement a very simple indicator component 
which can globally used as a plug in and which looks more attractive. I used a very simple code for that, but the result comes good.
we can easily replace UIActivityIndicator from this. Because it is a replacement for UIActivityIndicatorView, basically custom UIActivityIndicatorView.

just drag and drop the GAIndicator folder to your code, go to ViewController.m and copy this 3 lines on viewDidLoad which is the code to initialize and use the 
GAIndicator .  calling startAnimation & stopAnimation can be done as UIActivityIndicatorView. 

No copy rights for this you can use any where any how... :-)


Thanks!